Guide to the Alfred E. Kahn papers, 1942-1994
Kahn, Alfred E. papers, 1942-1994
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Alfred E. Kahn papers, 1942-1994.
4055
Alfred Edward, Kahn 1917-2010
34.6 cubic ft.
Thesis notes and typescripts, legal records, administrative files, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes notes and typescripts of Kahn's Ph.D. thesis, The Position of Great Britain in the World Economy, 1942; drafts of The Economics of Regulation, 1970; records concerning his participation in natural gas regulation hearings before the Federal Power Commission, ca.1956-1970; and his participation in proceedings involving a Honolulu anti-trust case, n.d. Also material from Cornell years, including files on Economics Department, Deanship of College of Arts and Sciences, and the Kahn-Bowers Report.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Economist, professor of economics at Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes notes and typescripts of Kahn's Ph.D. thesis, The Position of Great Britain in the World Economy, 1942; drafts of The Economics of Regulation, 1970; records concerning his participation in natural gas regulation hearings before the Federal Power Commission, ca.1956-1970; and his participation in proceedings involving a Honolulu anti-trust case, n.d. Also material from Cornell years, including files on Economics Department, Deanship of College of Arts and Sciences, and the Kahn-Bowers Report.
Includes Kahn's testimony in United States District Court regarding anti-trust actions pertaining to several cereal companies.
Also, a poem, "Mountain Talk," written by Archie Ammons for Alfred Kahn and inscribed to him, August 1972. Two cartoons and a certificate.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kahn, Alfred Edward, 1917-; Kahn, Alfred Edward. Economics of regulation.
Subjects:
Anti-trust law.; Economics.; Natural gas--Law and legislation.; Price regulation.; Economists.
Form and Genre Terms:
First drafts.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Personal Correspondence
Series II. The Economics of Regulation
Series III. NY Public Service Commission
Series IV. US Civil Aeronautics Board
Series V. White House Personal Subject Files
Series VI. White House Correspondence
Series VII. White House Dissertation
Series VIII. White House
Series IX. Speeches
Series X. Publications
Series XI. Correspondence
Series XII. Statements & Testimonies
Series XIII. Kahn's Subject Files Alpha
Series XIV. Fireman's Fund
Series XV. Articles
Series XVI. Miscellaneous Documents
Series XVII. Initial Collection Acquisition
Series XVIII. Videos
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Personal Correspondence
  - Kahn-Fidential 1943-48, 1943-48 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Kahn-Fidential 1951-June' 1953, 1951-53 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Kahn-Fidential 1956-Jan.' 1963, 1956-63 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Kahn-Fidential Jan.' 1963-June' 1966, 1963-66 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Kahn-Fidential June' 1966-, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Swedish Govr. Report on the International Oil Cartel, 1945 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Letters & Emails, 1960s (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Northwestern Conference "Economics of Petroleum Distrubution", 1966 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Northwestern Conference "Economics of Petroleum Distrubution", 1968 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Kahn Economics Vol. 2, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Draft of Preface, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 2, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Artwork Vol. 1, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 3-4, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 5, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 6, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - The Economics of Regulation: Principles and Institutions, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Part II: Economic Principles of Ratemaking, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Index, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - A-D, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - A-D, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - F-K, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - F-K, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - F-K, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - L-P, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - L-P, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - L-P, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - L-P, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Q-Z, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Q-Z, 1980-1982 (Box 130, Folder 11)
- Series II. The Economics of Regulation
  - Chapter 1, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 2, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 3, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 4, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 5, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 6, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 7, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 8, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 9, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 10, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 11, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 12, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 13, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 25, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Regulation Book - Reviews, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Public Control Test, 1970 - 71 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Series III. NY Public Service Commission
  - Monthly Report to the Gov., 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Deferred Fuel, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Destructive Competition, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Gas Deregulation FPC Opinion 770, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Gas Deregulation, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Gas Pricing, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Government Financing, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Interest During Construction, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Natural Gas Incremental Cost Pricing, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Oil Supply and Taxes, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Open Meetings, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Peak-Load Pricing, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Incremental Cost Responsibility Off-Peak Consumption, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Practices, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Former Students, 1974 - 77 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Munites of Conference 9/3/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Munites of Conference 9/4/75, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Munites of Conference 9/8/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Munites of Conference 9/9/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Munites of Conference 9/11/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Munites of Conference 9/12/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Munites of Conference 9/24/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Munites of Conference 10/6/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Munites of Conference 10/8/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Munites of Conference 10/10/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Munites of Conference 10/14/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Munites of Conference 10/15/75, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Munites of Conference 2/2/76 2nd Ed., 1976 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Munites of Conference 2/2/76 3rd Ed., 1976 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Munites of Conference 2/4/76, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Munites of Conference 3/31/76, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Power Pooling, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Rates, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Rates, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Rate of Return, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Rate of Return, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Public Financing and Ownership, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Public Power, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Public Utility Pricing, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Public Utilities: Rate Structure, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Regulated Industries, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Regulatory Research Institute, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Specialized Common Carriers, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Section 7, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Separations, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Separations, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Telpak, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - TV networks, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - The Test Year, 1974-1977 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Depreciation- LRIC Case 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Interruptible Rates and Load Mgt. C. 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Inverse Elasticity Generic Hearings C. 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Moving with Deliberate Speed. C 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Needle Peaks Generic Hearings- C 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Second Best Generic Hearings C 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Treatment of Taxes C. 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Generic Hearing on Incremental Cost Pricing, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Generic Hearings 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Inflation of Capital Costs, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Integration, Public Utilities, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Interconnection, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Interconnection: Revenue Sharing, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Law and Society, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - LOLP in LRIC Computations, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Long Range Incremental Costs, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - LMFBR, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Macro Conditions, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Management Efficiency, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Marginal Cost, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - MCI, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - MCI, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - Natural Gas Reserve, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - National Power Survey, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - NY Stock Exchange, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 25)
  - Oil Price, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 26)
  - Oil Ultimate Reserve, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 27)
  - Oligopoly, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 28)
  - OPEC, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 29)
  - Patents and Antitrust, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 30)
  - Peak Load Pricing, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 31)
  - Postal Rates, 1974-1977 (Box 124, Folder 32)
  - Time-of-Day Metering (6), 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1A)
  - Time-of-Day Metering (6), 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1B)
  - Time-of-Day Metering (6), 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 1C)
  - Telpak (6), 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Undergrounding, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Unemployment, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Uranium, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Water, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Criteria, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Western Electric, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 9A)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 9B)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1974-1977 (Box 125, Folder 9C)
  - Antitrust Suits, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Administered Prices and Inflation, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - AJW (6), 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Above 890, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Air Transportation, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Base Load, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Capital Requirements, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Carterfore, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Combination Companies, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Communications, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Communication Satellites - Domestic, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Communications Satellite Corp. FCC Docket No. 16070, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Comsat, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Compulsory Interconnection, Electricity #6, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Concentration, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Conglomerate Integration, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Conservation Clause (6), 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Consolidated Taxes, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Energy Industry Study Advisory Committee Meeting, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - Cost of Capital, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - Cost of Capital in LRIC (+Generally), 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - Cost-Benefit Analysis, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - Cream Skimming, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - Disposable Containers, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 24)
  - Distribution of Income, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 25)
  - Docket 18920, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 26)
  - Domestic Satellite, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 27)
  - Efficiency, 1974-1977 (Box 126, Folder 28)
  - Energy [1], 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1A)
  - Energy [1], 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1B)
  - Energy [1], 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1C)
  - Energy [1], 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 1D)
  - Energy [2], 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 2A)
  - Energy [2], 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 2B)
  - Energy [2], 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 2C)
  - Energy [2], 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 2D)
  - Environment, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Electric Rate Reform Bills (Testimony 7/27/77), 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Electric Power and Antitrust (6), 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Electricity Notes, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - FPC--New Gas Rates, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Generic Rate Hearing Prehearing Conference - Albany, N.Y. April 30, 1975 (-Briefs), 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Generic Rate Hearing Prehearing Conference - Albany, N.Y. April 30, 1975 (Case 26806 AEK First Draft), 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Aggregate Revenue Requirements C. 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Conservation Section Generic Hearings - C. 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Day-Night Rates C. 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Generic Hearings - Defining Systems, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - C. 26806 - Demand Elasticity, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Generic Hearings Discrimination, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Distribution Costs Generic Hearings - C. 26806, 1974-1977 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Minutes of Case Hearing 26806 and 26887, 1974-1977 (Box 128, Folder 1-12)
  - Minutes of Case Hearing 26806 and 26888, 1974-1977 (Box 129)
- Series IV. US Civil Aeronautics Board
  - ATA Speech San Francisco, Oct. 30, 1978, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Pictures, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - CAB - Air Cargo, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Predatory Pricing, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - CAB Congratulatory Letters, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Chairman's Weekly Meetings, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Sen. Kennedy Committee on Airline Washington, DC - Feb. 6, 1975, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Press Release, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - The Future of the CAB, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Travel Weekly Article, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Steve Salop (Monopoly/Duopoly), 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Buckley Letters, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Inflation, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - CAB, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Various Memos by Chairman Kahn Jun 15 - Sept. 30, 1977, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Letters to the Chairman, 1977 - 78 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - CAB - Correspondence, 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Overbooking, 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence "D", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence "E", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence "F", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence "H", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence "I", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence "J", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence "K", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence "L", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Kahn's Files, 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence "S", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence "T", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence "U", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence "V", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence "W", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence "X", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence "Y", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence "Z", 1977 - 78 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Investigation into Competitive marketing of air transportation agreements phases, 1985 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Regulatory actions (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 135, Folder 4)
- Series V. White House Personal Subject Files
  - Accelerated Depreciation, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - AFUDC (Accounting for Funds Used During Construction), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture - Dept. of #1 (Beef USDA), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Dairy - USDA, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Potato Diversion - USDA, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture - Dept. of #2 (Meat USDA), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Airlines, 1979 - 80 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Aspen Energy Conference - Summer 1980, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Anti-trust, 1978 - 82 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Autos (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Auto Bumper Standards, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Benzene, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1980 - 82 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Cassandrus - Regulatory, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Child Nutrition, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Chrysler, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Coal, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Coin, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Collective Bargaining Committee, 1978 - 79 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Common Cause (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Communications, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Comparative Inflation Rates, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Congressional, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Consultations, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Consultations, Labor, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - COWP, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Credit Controls, 1979 - 80 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - deButts Letter & Attachments, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Davis-Bacon, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Joel Dirlam Correspondence, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Economic Revitalization Board, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - EPG - Memoranda, 1979 - 80 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - EPG Agenda, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - EPG Minutes, 1979 - 80 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Electric Utilities, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Energy, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Energy Coordinating Committee (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Energy Modeling Forum, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Environmental, 1978 - 79 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - EPA, 1978 - 79 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - EXXON, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - FCC, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - FTC - Federal Trade Comm., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Feige, Ed, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Financial Markets, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Fiscal Policy, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Food, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - GM - UAW, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Gasoline, 1979 - 80 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Health Costs (1), 1979 - 80 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Health Costs (2), 1979 - 80 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Housing, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Industrial Policy, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Illinois Brick, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Inflation, 1979 - 80 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Inflation Strategy, 1979 - 80 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Insurance, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1978 - 79 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Kahn, Hannah - Reviews, 1979 - 80 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Kemeny Report, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Labor Dept., 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Labor Department/OSHA, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Labor/Management Cooperation, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Priorities, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - MACRO, 1979 - 80 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Mandatory Controls, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - MAP (Market Anti-inflation Plan) Abba Lerner Paper, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Maritime, 1978 - 79 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Monopoly, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Minimum Wage, 1978 - 80 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Mining, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Monetary Policy, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - National Commission for Review of Antitrust Laws & Procedures, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - National Health Ins., 1979 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Natural Gas, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - NERA, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - National Science Foundation, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - No Fault Insurance Program, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Normalization, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Nuclear Power, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Occupational Licensing, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Oil Import Quota, 1979 - 84 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Oil Shale, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Ozone, 1978 - 89 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Pay Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Personal, 1978 - 79 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Personal - Communications, 1974 - 80 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Petroleum, 1978 - 79 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Petroleum Refining, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Involvement, 1979 - 80 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Presidential Memoranda (1), 1978 - 79 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Presidential Memoranda (2), 1978 - 79 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Postal Electronic, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Price Advisory Committee, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Price Index CPI - Consumer Price Index Jan. 1980 through Dec. 1980, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Price Index PPI - Producer Price Index Jan. 1980 through Dec. 1980, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Price Index PPI - Producer Price Index Jan. 1979 through Dec. 1979, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Productivity, 1979 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Profits, 1979 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Profit Sharing, 1979 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Publicitity Related Corresponce, 1978 - 79 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Railroads, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Recommendations & Recruitment, 1979 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Regulation Q, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Regulatory Reform, 1979 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - RARG, 1979 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Real Wage Insurance, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Retailers, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Sanctions, 1979 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Shopping Lists, 1978 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Social Security, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Soft Drinks/Beer Industries, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Standards, Wage/Price '78 - '79, 1978 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - State/Local Cooperation, 1979 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Steel, 1979 - 80 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Stockpiles, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Structural Employment, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Style Memo (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Sugar, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Support Letters, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Tax, 1979 - 85 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Teamsters, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Textiles, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Timber, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - TIP, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Transportation - Dept. Of, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Trucking, 1975 - 82 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Utility Oil Backout, 1979 - 80 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Veterans Bill, 1978 - 79 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Wages, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Water, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Harry Walker Agency, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Weekly Reports & Presidential Summaries, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - White House Souvenirs, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Series VI. White House Correspondence
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - A, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - B, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - C, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - D, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - E, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - F, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - G, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - H, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - I, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - J, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - K, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - L, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - M, 1978 - 80 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - N, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - O, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - White House Alphabetical Chron. - P, 1978 - 80 (Box 21, Folder 3)